♪♪♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO STAY ♪
♪ 'TIL I'M IN THE GRAVE ♪
♪ 'TIL I ROT AWAY,
DEAD AND BURIED ♪
♪ 'TIL I'M IN THE CASKET
YOU CARRY ♪
♪ IF YOU GO, I'M GOING TOO, UH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IT WAS ALWAYS YOU,
ALRIGHT ♪
♪ AND IF I'M TURNING BLUE,
PLEASE DON'T SAVE ME ♪
♪ NOTHING LEFT TO LOSE
WITHOUT MY BABY ♪
♪ BIRDS OF A FEATHER, WE SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER, I KNOW ♪
♪ I SAID I'D NEVER THINK
I WASN'T BETTER ALONE ♪
♪ CAN'T CHANGE THE WEATHER,
MIGHT NOT BE FOREVER ♪
♪ BUT IF IT'S FOREVER,
IT'S EVEN BETTER ♪
♪ AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M CRYING FOR ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK
I COULD LOVE YOU MORE ♪
♪ IT MIGHT NOT BE LONG,
BUT BABY, I ♪
♪ I'LL LOVE YOU 'TIL THE DAY
THAT I DIE ♪
♪ 'TIL THE DAY THAT I DIE ♪
♪ 'TIL THE LIGHT
LEAVES MY EYES ♪
♪ 'TIL THE DAY THAT I DIE ♪
♪ I WANT YOU TO SEE, HM ♪
♪ HOW YOU LOOK TO ME, HM ♪
♪ YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
IF I TOLD YA ♪
♪ YOU WOULD KEEP
THE COMPLIMENTS I THROW YA ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE
SO FULL OF SHIT, UH ♪
♪ TELL ME IT'S A BIT, OH ♪
♪ SAY YOU DON'T SEE IT,
YOUR MIND'S POLLUTED ♪
♪ SAY YOU WANNA QUIT,
DON'T BE STUPID ♪
♪ AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M CRYING FOR ♪
♪ I DON'T THINK
I COULD LOVE YOU MORE ♪
♪ MIGHT NOT BE LONG,
BUT BABY, I ♪
♪ DON'T WANNA SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ BIRDS OF A FEATHER, WE SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER, I KNOW
('TIL THE DAY THAT I DIE) ♪
♪ I SAID I'D NEVER THINK
I WASN'T BETTER ALONE ('TIL
THE LIGHT LEAVES MY EYES) ♪
♪ CAN'T CHANGE THE WEATHER,
MIGHT NOT BE FOREVER ♪
♪ ('TIL THE DAY THAT I DIE)
BUT IF IT'S FOREVER,
IT'S EVEN BETTER ♪
♪ I KNEW YOU IN ANOTHER LIFE ♪
♪ YOU HAD THAT SAME LOOK
IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU,
DON'T ACT SO SURPRISED ♪
♪♪♪
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]